In this video we're going to talk about how one takes the type checking rules and
在这段视频中，我们将讨论如何采用类型检查规则和
translates them into an implementation. The high level overview of cool type
将它们转换为实现。酷型高级概述
checking is that it can be implemented in a single traversal over the abstract
检查是否可以在抽象的单次遍历中实现
syntax tree. And there's actually two phases here. There's the top down phase,
语法树。这里实际上有两个阶段。有一个自上而下的阶段，
in which the type environment is passed down the tree. And there's a bottom up
其中类型环境沿树向下传递。有一个自下而上的
phase in which the types are passed back up. So we start at the root of the tree
类型向上传递的阶段。所以我们从树根开始
with an initial type environment, this type of environment is passed down
对于初始类型环境，此类型的环境会被传递
recursively through the various nodes of the abstract syntax tree until we hit the
递归地遍历抽象语法树的各个节点，直到我们遇到
leaves. And starting at the leaves we use the environment to compute the types of
树叶。从树叶开始，我们使用环境来计算
each sub-expression working our way back up the tree to the root. Let's start our
每个子表达式都沿着树向上追溯到根。让我们开始我们的
discussion of the implementation of cool type checking with one of the simpler
用一种更简单的方法实现凉爽类型检查的探讨
rules in the type system, the rule for addition. And let's just briefly review
类型系统中的规则，用于加法的规则。让我们简单回顾一下
what this rule says. It says that the type check E one plus E two, we first have to
这条规则是怎么说的。上面说型式检查是E一加E二，我们首先要
type check E one, and then we have to type check the sub expression E two. And both
键入check E one，然后我们必须键入Check子表达式E2。而且两者都有
of those sub expressions have to have type end. And if they do then we can conclude
子表达式的类型必须为End。如果他们这么做了，那么我们就可以得出结论
that the overall expression, the sum of the two sub expressions, also has type A.
整体表达式，也就是两个子表达式的和，也是A型的。
And furthermore, this type checking is carried out in some environment. In this
此外，还在一些环境中进行了这种类型的检查。在这里面
case, the environment is the same for the entire expression and both sub
大小写时，整个表达式和两个子表达式的环境是相同的
expressions. Just, just to remind you, there's always an object environment for
表情。只是，只是提醒你，总有一个对象环境
the object names and scope, a method environment for the methods of the various
对象的名称和作用域、各种方法的方法环境
classes and we always need to know the current class. Now how will we implement
类，我们总是需要知道当前的类。现在我们将如何实现
this? Well we will have a recursive function called type check It takes two
这?我们将有一个名为type check的递归函数，它需要两个
arguments, it takes an [inaudible] environment and this will be a record, I'm
争论，这需要一个[听不见]的环境，这将是一个记录，我
not specifying exactly how this record is declared but it is essentially going to be
没有具体说明此记录是如何声明的，但它本质上将是
three parts m, o, and c. And it also takes an expression, and so here we are just
由m，o和c三部分组成，它也需要一个表达式，所以我们在这里
doing the case here where the expression is E1 + E2. And what should the code look
在这里做表达式是E1+E2的情况。代码应该是什么样子？
like? Well, we can pretty much just read the rule and translate directly into code,
喜欢?嗯，我们几乎可以直接阅读规则并将其转换成代码，
and this is one of the nice things about the notation for type systems, is that it
这是类型系统表示法的优点之一，就是它
really tells you very, very clearly how to write the implementation from the
确实非常、非常清楚地告诉您如何从
description. So what's the first thing we have to do? Well we have to type-check the
描述。那么我们要做的第一件事是什么呢？嗯，我们得打字检查一下
sub expression E1. And we can see from the rule that the environment in which E1 is
子表达式E1。我们可以从规则中看到E1所处的环境
type checked is exactly the same as the environment of E1 plus E2. So we just pass
勾选的类型与E1加E2的环境完全相同。所以我们就这么过去了
whatever our original environment argument was for E1 plus E2. We pass an, an
不管我们最初的环境论点是E1加E2。我们经过一个，一个
argument on, to a recursive call of the type check, to type check the sub
参数，传递给类型check的递归调用，以键入check sub
expression E1. And that type-checking will run and it will return some type T1, and
表达式E1。类型检查将运行，它将返回某个类型t1，并且
we don't know that T1 is an integer at this point. We're gonna have to check
在这一点上，我们不知道t1是一个整数。我们得检查一下
that, so we just remember what the type of E1 is. And, furthermore we type check E2,
所以我们只要记住E1的类型就行了。此外，我们还键入check E2，
okay? And that also happens in the same environment, we can see that here in the
好吧?而这也发生在相同的环境中，我们可以在这里看到
rule. And again we'll get back some type for E2, so type T2. And then we confirm
规则。再一次，我们会得到E2的一些类型，所以输入T2。然后我们确认
that both T1 and T2 are type integer. And we could have done a, the track that T1
T1和T2都是整型。我们可以做一个T1的轨道
is, is int a, right away, right after we had the type check T1 that would be a fine
is，is int a，就在我们进行类型检查t1之后，这将是一个罚款
thing to do. Here just to save space on the slide I have to clip the checks for T1
要做的事。这里只是为了节省幻灯片上的空间，我必须剪裁T1的支票
and T2 a, on one line. And if that check succeeds. If it doesn't succeed,
和t2a，在一条线上。如果检查成功的话。如果不成功，
presumably there should be some code in here, to, print out an error message But
大概这里应该有一些代码，用来打印出一条错误消息，但是
if that, if both T1 and T2 are in fact integers, than the type of the whole
如果这样，如果t1和t2实际上都是整数，那么整体的类型
expression is also an integer. So that's what's returned by this call, by the
表达式也是整数。这就是这个调用返回的内容，由
outermost call here, to the type check function. So now let's take a look at a
这里最外层的调用是对类型检查函数的调用。那么现在让我们来看一看
somewhat more complex type checking rule and its implementation. Here's the rule
稍微复杂一些的类型检查规则及其实现。规则是这样的
for a net with initialization. So we're declaring a variable x, of type t. And
对于具有初始化的网络。所以我们声明了一个变量x，类型为t。
that's going to be visible in the expression E1. But before we execute E1,
这将在表达式E1中可见。但在我们执行E1之前，
we're going to initialize X to the value of E0. And then after we've evaluated the
我们要将X初始化为E0的值。然后在我们评估完
entire let expression, we expect to get back something of type T1 And now, for all
整个let表达式，我们希望返回t1类型的内容，现在，
of that to work out. A few things have to be satisfied and those are listed as
来解决这个问题。有几件事必须得到满足，下面列出了
premises here of the rule. First of all E0 has to have some type T0 which is a
规则的前提在这里。首先，E0必须有某种类型T0，它是
subtype of T. And that's to guarantee that this initialization is correct, that X can
子类型，这是为了保证这个初始化是正确的，X可以
actually hold something of E0's type. And, for the entire expression to have type T1,
实际上持有的是E0类型的东西。并且，对于要具有类型T1的整个表达式，
well then E1 has to have type T1. But that type checking is carried out in an
那么E1必须有T1类型。但是该类型检查是在
environment that's extended with the declaration for X. So we, so we also know
使用X的声明来扩展的环境。所以我们，所以我们也知道
within E1, that X has type T. So now let's write the type-checking case for this. So
在E1中，X具有类型T。所以现在让我们为它编写类型检查用例。所以
the function type check is again is gonna take an environment as argument, and now
函数类型检查将再次将环境作为参数，现在
we're doing a case for a led with initialization. So, just reading of the,
我们在做一个带有初始化功能的LED的案子。所以，只要读一读，
the rules and what the conditions are that we have to check, we can see that one of
我们要检查的规则和条件是什么，我们可以看到其中一个
the first things we have to do, or one of the things we have to do, is to check that
我们要做的第一件事，或者说我们必须做的其中一件事，就是检查
E zero has some type T zero. So we just have a recursive call to type check here.
E0有某种类型的T0。所以我们在这里只有一个对类型check的递归调用。
This is carried out in the same environment as the overall expression. So
这是在与整体表达式相同的环境中执行的。所以
we just pass the environment on to the recursive call And now we're just type
我们只是将环境传递给递归调用，现在我们只需键入
checking E zero and we record its type T zero. So the second premise is implemented
检查E0，我们记录它的类型T0。所以第二个前提就实现了
like this. Now we're type checking E1 and we expect it to have some type T1, but now
像这样。现在我们正在检查e1的类型，我们希望它有某种类型t1，但是现在
the environment is different, so we're taking the original environment, the
环境是不同的，所以我们把原来的环境，
overall environment of the expression and we're adding, a declaration that X has
表达式的整体环境，我们正在添加X具有的声明
type T to that environment. So we're extending the environment, with an
在该环境中键入T。所以我们正在扩展环境，通过一个
additional variable declaration. Okay? And so we do that type checking call, and we
其他变量声明。好吧?所以我们做了类型检查调用，我们
get back a type T1. Now, we have to check that T0 is a sub-type of T. So that's a,
找回T1类型。现在，我们必须检查T0是否是T的一个子类型，所以这是a，
that's a call to some function that implements the sub-typing relationship,
这是对实现子类型关系的某些函数的调用，
and if, if that passes, if that check passes, well then we're done. And we can
如果，如果通过了，如果检查通过了，那么我们就完了。我们可以
return the type T1. And there's a little mistake here on the slide, there shouldn't
返回类型t1。幻灯片上有个小错误，不应该有
be a semicolon there. S o we just return T1 as the type of the entire expression.
在那里要用分号。所以我们只返回t1作为整个表达式的类型。